rebelsnotes.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy - Smut Marathon

### Who we are

There is no ‘we’, only I, Marie Rebelle, and my websites are [Rebel’s Notes](http://rebelsnotes.com/ "Rebel's Notes"), [Wicked Wednesday](http://wickedwednesday.rebelsnotes.com/ "Wicked Wednesday") and the [Smut Marathon](http://smut.rebelsnotes.com/ "Smut Marathon").

This privacy policy applies to these three sites.

### Protecting your privacy

I am a strong believer of protecting the privacy of all my visitors, which means your personal information will never be used beyond the permissions you give me or as required by law.

On my sites, as mentioned above, personal data may be collected, processed and used. The way your information is used is to contact you regarding the services you have requested and/or to offer you services, and/or to provide the services you have requested. This includes comments and subscriptions to any or all of the websites and the weekly newsletter. Rebel’s Notes, Wicked Wednesday and the Smut Marathon may employ trusted third party specialists to process and use your data on our behalf in order to deliver content to you in a more efficient manner.

### What personal data is collected and why?

#### _Comments_

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. We reserve the right to publish comments made on the Rebel’s Notes, Wicked Wednesday and the Smut Marathon websites. The website requires an email address to comment, but we will never publish your email address. You may use any email address to comment. The WordPress software records the IP address of your device when you comment, but that IP address is never published and will be removed from our system if you request to have all of your data removed.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available [here](https://automattic.com/privacy/ "Gravatar"). After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

#### _Media_

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

#### _Contact forms & Newsletter_

Readers who choose to subscribe to my newsletter, or complete any of my online forms, may be asked to supply personal data. If they choose to do so, that information is recorded and used for broad demographic information.

Your data will never be used for anything beyond the reason stated and the permissions you grant me. To alter the emails which you receive from me, including unsubscribing from all email communications, please [visit this page](http://rebelsnotes.com/contact/ "Contact Marie"). Make sure that you enter exactly the same e-mail address as you used to sign up. Alternatively, there is always an unsubscribe link in the footer of the newsletter.

#### _Embedded content from other websites_

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

#### _Analytics_

Rebel’s Notes, Wicked Wednesday and the Smut Marathon also uses Google Analytics to help me expand my reach on the internet to grow traffic, all IP address information is anonymized.  
You can find the Google Analytics Privacy Policy [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy "Google Analytics").

### How long is your data retained?

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so your follow-up comments can be recognized and approved automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

### What rights do you have over your data?

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can [request](http://rebelsnotes.com/contact/ "Contact Marie") to receive an exported file of the personal data I hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request for any personal data held about you to be erased. This does not include any data necessary to be kept for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Hosting

My three websites, [Rebel’s Notes](http://rebelsnotes.com/ "Rebel's Notes"), [Wicked Wednesday](http://wickedwednesday.rebelsnotes.com/ "Wicked Wednesday") and the [Smut Marathon](http://smut.rebelsnotes.com/ "Smut Marathon") are hosted in the Netherlands, with YourHosting. You can find there privacy policy [here](https://www.yourhosting.nl/over-ons/privacy-policy.html "YourHosting").

_Last update: 27.05.2018_
